

## **NGUYEN VAN A**

## **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and hữ cho tới đủ thì thôi, khiến cho lipsum.com trở of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. us id quod maxime placeat facere possimus, omnis voluptas assumenda est, om administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

## **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult because it is p and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to g a custom suit without taking measurements. Kristina Halvorson notes: goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

## **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer và đã nghiên c' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US e irur

## **REFERENCES**



## **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

## **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt to secure other greater pleasures, or else he endures pains to avoid worse pains." help@lipsum. and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities